Southern Coalition on Jails and Prisons; Records apap200
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Southern Coalition on Jails and Prisons Records
1970-1992
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap200
10.5 cubic ft. plus 1 banner
Organized in 1974, the Southern Coalition on Jails and Prisons was formed to promote greater awareness of the problems of prisons and corrections, improve communication between the prison population and the outside world, and advocate for alternatives to the death penalty.
Historical Note
Formed in 1974, the Southern Coalition for Jails and Prisons (SCJP) began its work with a focus on general prisoners' rights. Within the first two to three years of its existence, the coalition's members narrowed their mission to focus more specially on abolition of the death penalty -- not to the exclusion of other prison issues like basic healthcare and visitation rights, but with particular care given to those on death row in the American South. One of their other major projects was advocating for alternatives to incarceration in order to reduce growing numbers in the prison population.
The coalition's director, Joe Ingle, is a North Carolina native and graduate of St. Andrew's College who became a minister of the United Church of Christ [Gaillard, Frank. "Death Watch: The Final Hours of Frank Coppola". From Frank Coppola file].
Driven by religious, legal, and ethical convictions, Ingle devoted countless hours to providing myriad methods of support to convicted prisoners and their families. While offering spiritual guidance, he also connected prisoners with defense attorneys who would put sincere effort into achieving justice for the accused, whether it was a death sentence commuted to life in prison or the recognition of evidence proving complete innocence. Though described as soft-spoken and gentle, Ingle faced the public spotlight countless times as he and SCJP supporters spoke before the press, conducted letter and petition campaigns, staged protests on behalf of Death Row prisoners, and generally defended the position of the Southern Coalition. Ingle also published a book in 1990 entitled Last Rights: 13 Fatal Encounters With the State's Justice, which details his experiences supporting Death Row inmates and encourages readers to see the prisoners as human beings who need help. The book was re-released in May of 2008 with a new foreword by M*A*S*H star Mike Farrell as well as the original foreword by William Styron [Death Penalty Information Center. Resources/Books. "Last Rights: 13 Fatal Encounters With the State's Justice". Accessed 8 February 2010 from http://www.deathpenaltyinfo.org/books].
In more than fifteen years of existence, the Southern Coalition gained several official affiliates through the south, including (but not limited to) the Clearinghouse on Georgia Prisons and Jails, the Florida Clearinghouse on Criminal Justice, and the Alabama Prison Project [Letters from Southern Coalition Board of Directors members to affiliates, February 1990. (Board of Directors file, Series #1 -- Administrative)]. However, the Coalition was active in North Carolina, South Carolina, Georgia, Alabama, Mississippi, Tennessee, Arkansas, Florida, Louisiana, Virginia, and Kentucky through the early 1990s. Staff in the affiliate offices served as advocates for prisoners in their particular states and acted as liaisons between inmates and Ingle, who worked out of SCJP headquarters in Tennessee but traveled frequently within the United States to visit prisoners on Death Row. Ingle also made trips to Europe to connect with abolition advocates there.
The Southern Coalition on Jails and Prisons relied heavily on donations for the duration of its existence. Some funding came from private citizens who were contacted by the SCJP's direct mail campaign, or who became aware of specific prisoner's cases and decided to help anti-death penalty advocates. But the biggest support came from organizations whose mission was to distribute money to projects for social change. Some institutions gave money to the SCJP with great frequency, some gave sporadically over the years, and others regularly turned down the Coalition for various reasons. Ingle wrote many grant proposals over the years in order to keep the Southern Coalition running.
In 1990, the Edna McConnell Clark Foundation (one of the Southern Coalition's regular sources of funding) decided not to renew its grant support of the SCJP. This loss of major financial backing, in combination with burnout on Ingle's part, both contributed to the closing of the Southern Coalition's doors in late November 1990. By that time, Ingle had seen 19 prisoners -- people he considered friends -- face death by execution [Waddle, Ray. "17 years take toll: Ingle leaving his death row ministry". The Tennessean, 25 Nov. 1990. (Board of Directors file, Series #1 -- Administrative)].
When the SCJP ended its journey shortly before January 1, 1991, it left the care of its newsletter (The Southern Coalition Report) in the hands of the Alabama Prison Project. Affiliate offices in Virginia and North Carolina took over the direct mailing list, ensuring that foundations and individuals still interested in supporting criminal justice would be able to do so [Memo of Agreement, Board of Directors -- Southern Coalition for Jails & Prisons. Board of Directors file, Series #1 -- Administrative]. Meanwhile, Ingle accepted a fellowship at Harvard Divinity for the spring of 1991 as a stepping stone for figuring out "where the good Lord [wanted him] to go next" [Waddle, Ray. "17 years take toll: Ingle leaving his death row ministry". The Tennessean, 25 Nov. 1990. (Board of Directors file, Series #1 -- Administrative)].
Scope and Contents
The files of the Southern Coalition on Jails and Prisons (SCJP) cover the years 1974 to 1991, the latter being the year the Coalition closed down. Most of the material was maintained by the Coalition's director, Joe Ingle, and documents his work to abolish the death penalty and provide support for prisoners on Death Row. The SCJP collection is broken down into five series: administrative files, fundraising, prisoner case files, subject files, and memorabilia.
The collection includes a sampling of correspondence, financial documents, and mailing lists pertaining to the general operations of the Coalition over the years. Some documents originated with the Coalition's affiliate offices in other southern states, but most seem to be from the SCJP's headquarters. However, there is a distinct lack of financial papers and general correspondence for an agency that operated more than fifteen years, and many of the administrative records date from the years just prior to the end of the Southern Coalition's work. There are also just three issues of the Southern Coalition's newsletter in the collection.
Extensive files exist on individual prisoners who sought the Coalition's help. Those documents frequently contain correspondence from and about the prisoners, their legal histories, and life on Death Row. Many of the files include newspaper clippings maintained by Joe Ingle regarding developments in the prisoners' cases. Inmates who received more media attention at the time of their sentences, stays, and executions tend to have correspondingly larger files from the Southern Coalition.
The other sizable portion of the collection is the fundraising series. These are records of foundations that either donated money to the Southern Coalition or were solicited by them but could not (or would not) support the SCJP. Some institutions, like the Edna McConnell Clark Foundation and Playboy Foundation, were regular donors and played a large part in the Coalition's longevity. Most of the files contain correspondence between Ingle and the foundations.
The Southern Coalition collection also covers a wide array of related death penalty topics including collaborative efforts by Amnesty International, documents from the various branches of the Southern Coalition, articles written by Joe Ingle, and material collected by Ingle on his European People-to-People tour in the mid-1980s. Some publicity materials for Ingle's book Last Rights: 13 Fatal Encounters are also present, though there is no manuscript included. There is also a selection of anti-death penalty buttons and a banner used at protests.
Most of the collection was re-housed according to the folder labels that the Southern Coalition employed. Only a few folders with miscellaneous items inside were interfiled with existing folders. Also, many folders were overstuffed and had to be broken down into several sub-folders; those were labeled "1/2", "2/2", etc., depending on the level of breakdown needed.
Arrangement of the Collection
Divided into 4 topical series.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department Special Collections and Archives by Joseph Ingle in 2005.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted with the exception of one folder in series #3.
Death Penalty; Capital punishment--United States.; African Americans and Civil Rights Organizations; Criminal Justice and Prisons; Social Activists and Public Advocates; Ingle, Joseph B. (Joseph Burton), 1946-
- Administrative Files, 1981-1990; Undated; 1; 0.5 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains information on the daily, monthly, and yearly operational duties of the Southern Coalition on Jails and Prisons. There is a general correspondence file containing information about the day-to-day operations of the Coalition, a specific file dedicated to correspondence with the Law Offices of Woods and Woods, and material from the various boards of directors within the Coalition (including meeting minutes). There are also documents related to updates made to the Coalition's by-laws in the late 1980s.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Audited Financial Statements & other Financial Information, 1990 June 30 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Better Business Bureau - Solicitation Questionnaires, 1984; 1990 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors Letter Writing Campaign, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors Minutes & Agendas, June-December, 1988 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors Minutes & Agendas, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors Minutes & Agendas, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - BNA Travel - Activity Reports, 1988-1990 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Browning, Edmund (Bishop) - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Brochure - "Awakening the Conscience of a Nation", Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Bryan, Robert - National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, letter, Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Budget Rapid Printers, 1988; 1989; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - By-laws & Charter - Updates/Provisions, 1988 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - Career Development Center of the Southeast - Correspondence & Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - General, 1983-1990 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Law Offices of Woods & Woods, 1987-1990 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Direct Mail Program, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Director's Report - Alabama Prison Project, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Director's Report - Florida Clearinghouse on Criminal Justice, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - Director's Report - Georgia Clearinghouse on Prisons & Jails, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - Director's Report - North Carolina Prison & Jail Project, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - Director's Report - Tennessee - Southern Coalition for Jails and Prisons, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - Financial Papers: Budgets, Taxes, Contributions, 1981-1990 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 22)
  - Ingle, Joe - Awards & Recognition, 1988 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 23)
  - Irrevocable Power of Attorney Form, 1985 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - Newsletters & Mailing List, 1988; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - The Other Side - Special Issue, Giver's Guide, July/August, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 26)
  - Plan for Board Development, 1988 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 27)
  - Southern Coalition on Jails & Prisons Report, 1989 Spring (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 28)
  - Southern Magazine - Correspondence, 1988; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 29)
  - Trademark Documents for Southern Coalition Logo, 1987 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 30)
  - Whitesides, Henry - Legal Aid to Indigents, 1988 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 31)
  - Whittle Communications - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 32)
  - Wicker, Tom -NY Times - Correspondence & Articles, 1988 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 33)
- Fundraising, 1974-1990; Undated; 2; 3.25 cubic ft.
  The SCJP gained the attention of a diverse group of benefactors, including the Ford Foundation, the Rockefeller Brothers Fund, and the New World Foundation. Not every institution found in the fundraising series was a donor to the Coalition; some were solicited by Joe Ingle and his colleagues but did not have donating policies that included death penalty issues. Other institutions supported the anti-death penalty platform but could not stretch their funds to meet the Coalition's needs in a given year. Most of the material in this series is correspondence between foundation officials and Ingle, but there are also some grant proposals included. More grant proposals can be found in the subject files.
  - Aaron Diamond Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 34)
  - Abelard Foundation, 1989 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 35)
  - ARCA Foundation, 1987; 1989 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 36)
  - Article - "The 10 Most Common Organizational Problems....", 1983 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 37)
  - Ben and Jerry's Foundation, 1988 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 38)
  - Boston Foundation, 1987-1990 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 39)
  - Catholic Social Services, 1975 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 40)
  - Charles Merrill, 1986-1990 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 41)
  - Chicago Community Trust, 1983 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 42)
  - Chicago Resource Center, 1983-1990 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 43)
  - Church Women United, 1974-1982; 1985; 1986 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 44)
  - Columbia Foundation, 1983; 1986; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 45)
  - Couch, Jane - Fundraising Consultant, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 46)
  - Cummins Engine Foundation, 1977; 1979 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 47)
  - David and Lucille Packard Foundation, 1982-1984; 1986 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 48)
  - Day Foundation, 1977 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 49)
  - Denominational Support, 1975-1979 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 50)
  - Episcopal Church Center, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 51)
  - Edna McConnell Clark Foundation [1/9], 1977-1978 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 52)
  - Edna McConnell Clark Foundation [2/9], 1979 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 53)
  - Edna McConnell Clark Foundation [3/9], 1980 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 54)
  - Edna McConnell Clark Foundation [4/9], 1982 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 55)
  - Edna McConnell Clark Foundation [5/9], 1983-1984 (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 56)
  - Edna McConnell Clark Foundation [6/9], 1987 December (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 57)
  - Edna McConnell Clark Foundation [7/9], 1987 January-1987 November (Box 1 (2-Fundraising), Folder 58)
  - Edna McConnell Clark Foundation [8/9], 1985 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 1)
  - Edna McConnell Clark Foundation [9/9], 1988 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 2)
  - Ferry, Carol B., 1978-1990 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 3)
  - Field Foundation [1/2], 1974-1979 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 4)
  - Field Foundation [2/2], 1980-1989 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 5)
  - Florence V. Burden Foundation, 1983; 1987-1988 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 6)
  - Ford Foundation [1/3], 1976; 1979-1982 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 7)
  - Ford Foundation [2/3], 1983-1986 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 8)
  - Ford Foundation [3/3], 1987-1990 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 9)
  - Fund for Southern Communities, 1983-1989 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 10)
  - Funding Exchange, 1980-1983; 1985-1990 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 11)
  - Gannett Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 12)
  - Geraldine Dodge Foundation, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 13)
  - Hunt Alternatives Fund, 1984-1986 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 14)
  - Institute for Southern Studies, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 15)
  - Ittleson Foundation, 1974-1976; 1979; 1980; 1989-1990 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 16)
  - J. Roderick MacArthur Foundation [1/4], 1982-1985 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 17)
  - J. Roderick MacArthur Foundation [2/4], 1986 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 18)
  - J. Roderick MacArthur Foundation [3/4], 1987-1988 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 19)
  - J. Roderick MacArthur Foundation [4/4], 1989-1990 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 20)
  - Jewish Communal Fund of New York, 1976; 1978 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 21)
  - John D. & Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, 1981; 1983; 1984; 1986 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 22)
  - Joint Foundation Support [1/2], 1974-1981 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 23)
  - Joint Foundation Support [2/2], 1982-1983; 1985-1988 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 24)
  - Joyce Foundation, 1983 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 25)
  - Kathleen Price & J.M. Bryan Foundation, 1989 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 26)
  - Lakeview Presbyterian Church, 1980 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 27)
  - Levi Strauss Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 28)
  - Lewis Foundation, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 29)
  - Lilly Endowment, Inc., 1974-1975; 1980 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 30)
  - Lutheran Resources Commission, 1975 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 31)
  - Lyndhurst Foundation [1/2], 1979-1980 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 32)
  - Lyndhurst Foundation [2/2], 1982-1983; 1986-1988; 1990; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 33)
  - Mary Reynolds Babcock Foundation, 1987-1990 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 34)
  - Menninger Foundation, 1988-1990 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous Foundations/ Letters, 1974-1986 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 36)
  - Ms. Foundation for Women, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 37)
  - National Community Funds, 1983-1988 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 38)
  - Needmor Fund, 1977-1983 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 39)
  - New York Foundation, 1975-1979 (Box 2 (2-Fundraising), Folder 40)
  - New World Foundation, 1974-1982; 1984; 1986-1987 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 1)
  - Norman Foundation, 1976-1979 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 2)
  - North Shore Unitarian Church - Veatch Program [1/3], 1975-1980 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 3)
  - North Shore Unitarian Church - Veatch Program [2/3], 1981-1984 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 4)
  - North Shore Unitarian Church - Veatch Program [3/3], 1985-1986 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 5)
  - Playboy Foundation, Inc. [1/2], 1977-1983 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 6)
  - Playboy Foundation, Inc. [2/2], 1984-1990 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 7)
  - Partnership for Democracy, 1986-1987; 1988 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 8)
  - Presbyterian Center - Office of Women, 1980-1984 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 9)
  - Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program, 1978-1982; 1984-1988 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 10)
  - Public Welfare Foundation [1/3], 1979-1982 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 11)
  - Public Welfare Foundation [2/3], 1983-1987 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 12)
  - Public Welfare Foundation [3/3], 1988-1990 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1974-1982 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 14)
  - Stern Fund, 1975; 1977-1978; 1982 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 15)
  - Trinity Episcopal Church, 1974-1981; 1984; 1989-1990 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 16)
  - United Church of Christ, 1979-1987 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 17)
  - United Way, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 18)
  - W. Clement and Jessie Stone Foundation, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 19)
  - W.E. Walker Foundation, 1984-1989 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 20)
  - Z. Smith Reynolds Foundation, 1979-1985; 1987-1990 (Box 3 (2-Fundraising), Folder 21)
- Prisoner Case Files, 1973-1992; Undated; 3; 4.5 cubic ft.
  Ingle kept material documenting his interaction with the inmates he and his colleagues were trying to help. Some case files fit into one or two folders, but other high-profile cases (eg. Willie Darden, Timothy Baldwin) fill multiple folders and are divided into categories like correspondence and legal documents. Most files contain correspondence between inmates and Joe Ingle as well as letters to the inmates from family, friends, and sometimes members of the public. Copies of legal paperwork, especially affidavits, are often included. The case files of John Spenkelink, Willie Darden, and James Hill include photographs.
  Notes of interest: The file on Rocky Coker contains a standard cassette entitled "Things to Remember". Willie Darden's documents include his original, handwritten letter to family, friends, and supporters in the hours before he was executed in 1988. Joe Giarratano's correspondence folders have a (photocopied) note from Caroline Kennedy to Marie Deans of the Virginia Coalition on Jails and Prisons, as well as letters from celebrities like Joan Baez who supported the Southern Coalition's cause. (Kennedy note is in Giarratano correspondence folder 3 of 4; letter from Joan Baez is in Giarratano correspondence folder 4 of 4.).
  - Adams, James - General, 1979-1981; 1983-1984 (Box 3 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 22)
  - Adams, James - Legal Papers [1/2], 1977-1980 (Box 3 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 23)
  - Adams, James - Legal Papers [2/2], 1983-1984 (Box 3 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 24)
  - Adams, James - News Clippings, 1984 (Box 3 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 25)
  - Alfred, Leo Learie, 1978-1982; 1985; 1988 (Box 3 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 26)
  - Baldwin, Timothy - "After the Fact" Investigation Proposal, Undated (Box 3 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 27)
  - Baldwin, Timothy - Correspondence from Baldwin to Joe Ingle, 1982-1984 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 1)
  - Baldwin, Timothy - (General) Correspondence, Mailgrams, Press Releases, 1982; 1984 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 2)
  - Bakdwin, Timothy - Correspondence Received [1/2], 1982-1984 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 3)
  - Baldwin, Timothy - Correspondence Received [2/2], 1984 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 4)
  - Baldwin, Timothy - Legal Papers [1/2], 1982-1983 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 5)
  - Baldwin, Timothy - Legal papers [2/2], 1982-1983; Undated (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 6)
  - Baldwin, Timothy - Miscellaneous, 1984; Undated (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 7)
  - Baldwin, Timothy - News Clippings, 1982; 1984 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 8)
  - Baldwin, Timothy - Receipts, Notes & Ephemera, 1982-1984; Undated (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 9)
  - Baldwin, Timothy - Religious Support, 1982 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 10)
  - Barfield, Margie Velma - General, 1982-1984; 1988; Undated (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 11)